(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-30T00:22:57.803043",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
CCGG 劇場
[CCGG Theater]
曖昧3センチ そりゃぷにってことかい？ ちょっ！
Around 3 centimeters... is that squishy? Wait!
ラッピングが制服...だぁぁ不利ってこたない ぷ。
Wrapped in a uniform... no disadvantage at all!
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ そんときゃーっち＆Release ぎょっ
I'll try my best, do it! Catch & release then, gyo!
汗(Fuu)々(Fuu)の谷間に Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
In the gap of sweat, Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
なんかだーるー なんかでーるー あいしてーるー
Kinda sluggish, kinda out of it, "I love you"—
あれ一個が違ってるんるー
Wait, one of those was wrong!
悩みん坊ー 高鉄棒ー おいしんぼー いーかげんにシナサイ
Worrywart, high bar, foodie... cut it out already!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって 所謂ふつーのおニャのこ
Her flushed body after jumping... just a normal girl.
驚いたあたしだけ？ 豚骨ハリガネおかわりだだだ
Was I the only one surprised? Extra noodle refill!
BON-BON おーえん団 Let's get! チェリーパイ
BON-BON cheer squad! Let's get cherry pie!
RAN-RAN かんげー会 Look up! せんせーしょん
RAN-RAN welcome party! Look up! Sensation!
はい！ 存在感..小惑星 ぶつかって溶けましたぼーぜん
Yes! Asteroid presence... crashed and melted in shock!
大いに歌ってシレンジャー もっていけ！
Sing out loud, Syrenger! Take it with you!
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
The one who gets the last laugh will be me!
セーラーふくだからです←結論
Because of the sailor suit! ← Conclusion
月曜日なのに！ 機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
Even though it's Monday! What to do about this bad mood?
夏服がいいのです←キャ？ ワ！ イイv
Summer uniform is best! ← Eek? Wow! Great v
曖昧3センチ そりゃプニっとことかい ラウ！
Vague 3cm, does that mean squishy? Rawr!
ラッピングが制服？ よしコレってことない ポン！
Is the wrapping a uniform? Alright, no problem! Pop!
がんばっちゃった やっちゃっちゃ
I tried my best, I did it!
持っていけ！ 最後に笑っちゃうのは私のはず
Take it with you! The one laughing in the end should be me!
セーラーふくだからです 結論
Because it's a sailor uniform! Conclusion!
月曜日なのに 機嫌悪いの どうするよ？
Even though it's Monday, you're in a bad mood, what to do?
夏服がいいのです キャワイイ
Summer uniforms are better! So cute!
接近3ピッチ するまでチュッてだ やん！
Approach 3 pitches, a kiss until then, stop it!
がんばって！ 張り切って！ My Darling Darling Please!
Do your best! Get pumped! My Darling Darling Please!
モリモリ盛り上がり 恋したり まだナイショにしといて リミ！
Getting all hyped up, falling in love, keep it a secret for now, Rimi!
甘えん坊 用心棒 重心棒 調子こいて 玉砕！
Spoiled child, bodyguard, center of gravity, getting carried away and crushed!
プレゼント あいてに これいいでしょ 大げさに散らかしていこうにー はい！
Giving a present, isn't this nice? Let me scatter it in style, yes!
絶対残業 一番生意気する気が おねだり だだだだ！
Absolute overtime, feeling like the cheekiest, begging dadada!
買わんの？ そうで レッツゴー パーティで
Won't you buy it? That's right, let's go to the party!
イェイイェイ それだーっす！ What's up テンション オーイ！
Yay yay, that's it! What's up, tension, oi!
喪失感 全然 アルバイト探したら見つかって 当然
Feeling of loss, not at all, naturally found a part-time job!
人生 まるっと 蹴れナッシュ
Kicking life entirely!
やっってみの 新規に狙っちゃうのは 私の挑戦
Give it a try, targeting anew is my challenge!
セーラーふく 着替えても 私
Even if I change into a sailor uniform, I'm still me!
週末はどうよ？ チラ見せなんて ありきたり
How's the weekend? A peek is so cliché!
制服は 簡単よ
Uniforms are easy!
抱きしめたい
I want to hug you!
風邪っ冷め 抱きついて我慢だ ギュッ！
Catching a cold, endure it with a hug, tight!
プレとき！ マジとき！ シュガーシュガースイート！
Present time! Serious time! Sugar sugar sweet!
ボンボンボンボンで
Bon bon bon bon!
スイッチ！ ウッウッアー！
Switch! Uh uh ah!
ララン チョー チョーキー！
Lalan super super key!
Look up! フーフーハー！
Look up! Hoo hoo hah!
はい！ エデュケーション ラビ！
Yes! Education Navi!
ABC んだくだ んだくだ
ABC ndakuda ndakuda!
惚れて 惚れて フィナーレ！
Fall in love, fall in love, finale!
持っていけ！ 最後に
Take it with you! In the end...
笑っちゃうのは私のはず
The one laughing should be me!
セーラーふくだからです 結論
Because it's a sailor uniform! Conclusion!
月曜日なのに 機嫌悪いの
Even though it's Monday, you're in a bad mood...
どうするよ？
What to do?
夏服がいいのです キャワイイ
Summer uniforms are better! So cute!
やっぱりね 最後に
As expected, in the end...
笑っちゃうのは私のはず
The one laughing should be me!
セーラーふくだからです 結論
Because it's a sailor uniform! Conclusion!
曖昧3センチ それプニっとことかい ワオ！
Vague 3cm, does that mean squishy? Wow!
ラッピングが制服？ よしこれ職ことない ポン！
Is the wrapping a uniform? Alright, no problem! Pop!
がんばっちゃん！ やっちゃっちゃん！ あんときゃー ヴァージンでハイーっせ！
I tried my best! I did it! Back then I was a virgin, high!
ハッセ！ ハッセ！ 大好きだ ダーリン ダーリン ニュース！
Hasse! Hasse! I love you, darling darling news!
Wow! This is what I'm talking about!
That's what we need!
We need... We need another hit show!
We needed an anime opening!
No, no, we need... No, we need a show. We need something with substance.
I just thought that our show was failing because we didn't have an anime opening.
No, our show is failing cause it's REALLY bad.
It's... It's not that bad.
It's REALLY bad. Have you seen the reviews?
They're wrong, though. It's a loud minority opinion.
Ugh, well... That's so complicated. I didn't sign up for this. I'm just the eye candy. I can't...
Well, your eye candy isn't getting us any ratings!
Well, yours isn't either, because they're gone!
No, stop, stop! No one wants to see that! Stop! We need an idea.
We can both sell ourselves out!
No, that's not gonna work. That's not enough. I have an idea.
What?
We steal other people's concepts!
You're a genius!
We just make what's already popular...
And put our...
And put our name on it!
We'll get all the credit!
What are they gonna do?
Nothing!
We'll get all the funding back!
And then we can finally do what we're really passionate about!
Oh my God! Oh my God! But we're gonna have to do so much research on what's popular!
What do we do? What do we do? We need influencers!
We need influencers? We need...
...sexy ladies?
We have that. I guess we already have that.
I can ask my friends...
What else do we need?
We need to sell out.
Ah, I'm so tired from all this thinking.
I think we need to explore other genres to see if the grass is greener.
Like what?
Every genre.
I think that's the only way.
You're making me kind of...
What?
I was a sympathetic sleeper.
Where... Where are we, Gigi?
What is this?
What is this? Are we... Are we in my head? Wait, are we in your head?
Are we in my head?
This is just like Inception! This is just like Inception!
Does that mean we're gonna steal Mabel's ideas?
Oh no, they're our ideas. We're in my head.
Wait, this is my head. I'm gonna steal your idea!
You can't steal my ideas.
I could!
Wait, what if... What if I see every single idea that's in your head, and then I take them from you?
If you go too deep into my brain, you'll get to the yaoi part!
Oh, oh, maybe we should start with my brain. It's okay, it's okay.
Wait, wait! What's in your brain?
Um, actually, there's a lot in my brain. For example...
Your brain is full of bad romance novels! We can't put that in our show!
Yes, we can! Yeah, let's put it in our show! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Romance, hmm... Romance.
I guess we need to break free out of this place.
DROPPED OUT OF SCHOOL MUSICAL
[Title: DROPPED OUT OF SCHOOL MUSICAL]
THE FOLLOWING SCENE IS AS FOLLOWS: CROY AND GIBRIELLA ARE AT A PARTY. CROY LOVES BASKETBALL AND GIBRIELLA IS NOT LIKE OTHER GIRLS... A FICTIONAL TALE OF SONG AND BASKETBALL.
I don't want to sing! I'm... I'm just a normal boy!
I just want to play basketball with my friends and get my head in the game!
I can't sing! I'm just Troy!
Get it together, Gibriella!
We don't have time for extracurriculars, we have to get into college!
I'm not like other girls, I just want to stay at home and read books!
ばかみたい 子供なのね
So foolish, you're like a child.
夢を追って傷ついて
Chasing dreams and getting hurt.
嘘が下手なくせに
Even though you're terrible at lying,
笑えない笑顔みせた
you showed me a joyless smile.
I love you も ろくに言わない
You can't even say "I love you" properly,
口下手でほんまに不器用
so clumsy and bad with words.
なのになのにどうして
Even so, even so, why is it
サヨナラは言えたの
that you could say goodbye?
だめだね だめよ だめなのよ
It's no good, no good, it's no good at all.
あんたが好きで好きすぎて
I love you, I love you too much.
どれだけ強いお酒でも
No matter how strong the drink,
歪まない思い出が ばかみたい
my memories won't blur... What a fool I am.
ばかみたい 本当バカね
So foolish, truly a fool.
あんた信じるばかりで
All I ever did was believe in you.
強い女のふり
Pretending to be a strong woman,
切なさの夜風浴びる
bathed in the sorrowful night wind.
ひとりになって
I've been alone,
3年が過ぎ
for three years now,
街並みさえも 変わりました
and even the town around me has changed.
なのになのにどうして
Yet, why, oh why,
未練だけ置き去り
am I left here with nothing but regrets?
ほんまにロクな男やない
You really were a good-for-nothing guy.
揃いの指輪外します
I'll take off our matching ring.
ざまあみろせいせいするわ
Serves you right, I feel relieved.
いい加減 待ってても ばかみたい
Waiting for you any longer... I'm such a fool.
だめだね だめよ だめなのよ
It's no good, no good, no good at all.
あんたが好きで 好きすぎて
I love you, I love you way too much.
どれだけ強いお酒でも
No matter how strong the drink,
歪まない思い出が ばかみたい
these unyielding memories... I'm such a fool.
ほんまにロクな男やない
You really were a good-for-nothing guy.
揃いの指輪外します
I'll take off our matching ring.
ざまあみろせいせいするわ
Serves you right, I feel relieved.
なんなのよ この涙 ばかみたい
What are these tears? I'm such a fool.
Whoa, yeah, yeah! Musicals is where it's at!
I think... I think this could really be something...
This is gonna get us the big dollars!
Yeah, hopefully the big mouse is not gonna shoot us in the head...
10 billion dollars!
What big mouse?
Don't worry about it. 10 billion dollars!
Yeah, that's really good.
We might need like a different type of show too, you know? Just for variety...
...so they can't shut us down. / A variety show?
Yeah! Like a variety game show?
The Autofister Games.
The Autofister... Physical!
Games! / Physicals!
105!
But first, a word from our sponsors!
Whoa! Slow down there, partner!
Hold your horses!
Don't you think you're scrolling a little too fast?
Yeah, put down the phone and fullscreen our video instead,
because we are about to show you the new hottest thing in town!
Introducing the Autofister Network!
Get it? 'Cause it's Autofister Network, but this is our merch!
We wanted to take this opportunity to show you all of our cool, fun merch before it goes live!
We've got Cemimis, Gimimis, grems, Otomos...
...and this neat acrylic stand of the both of us!
And if you hurry up, you'll even be able to get the limited set with a hand-signed postcard by both of us!
Woohoo!
It will be live at this exact time,
so make sure to check it out then!
Coming soon to a stream near you!
And we're back from our commercial break!
Thank you, everyone, for waiting!
Welcome back to the official Autofister...
PHYSICAL AUTOFISTER!
100! 100!
And with us, we have our lovely contestants!
BAE! G'day! I'm gonna win! Ayy!
SUTEN!
スーちゃん頑張るぞー！
Su-chan will do her best!
TOWA-SAMA! トワ様！
TOWA-SAMA! Towa-sama!
As said before, we're here to find out who's the ultimate winner of...
Physical Autofister! 100!
As said before our commercial break, each contestant will have to compete in our physical obstacle course of FUN!
If you're just now tuning in, here is a quick recap!
Everyone starts in a line. You have to run to the other side while avoiding obstacles, and do a pre-decided physical activity.
Grab a question from a dragon who telepathically gives it to you in your brain, run back and answer the question! Yeah!
We'll do 4 rounds and the person with the most points at the end of 4 rounds is the WINNER!
Okay, well everyone get into position! Let's go!
What is this? So, as said before, of course...
...since a lot of these questions will be in English, they have the handicap.
What is this?! Nice! Nice!
Okay, okay, okay, everyone in position?
Yes, yes. The first run... The first round is you run over there...
...and do 5 jumping jacks.
走って、5ジャンプやって、質問とって、走って帰る。
Run, do 5 jumps, grab the question, and run back.
わかりましたか？ Okay!
Did you understand? Okay!
3! 2! 1! Go!
1! 2! 3! 4! 5!
Su-chan first!
Su-chan was first!
I was betrayed! Please read the question out loud.
Okay, えっと... Um, I like... Strawberry!
Okay, let's see... Um, I like... Strawberry!
Strawberry! She had to name a fruit! Name a fruit! Strawberry!
One point!
You can give me the questions over here.
Well, next round... Next round, is everyone ready?
No, no, no, we have to explain it. Yeah, but is everyone ready for the next round?
次のステップは何だろ？ No, not the crab walk like this?
What's the next step? No, not the crab walk like this?
Crab walk like this! Crab walk!
Come on! What?!
Crab walk and 5 squats!
Crab walk AND 5 squats?
Wait, do they have to jump?
Jump! They have to jump!
帰った時もこれ。帰るときも？ Okay.
On the way back too. On the way back too? Okay.
Okay, is everyone ready? 3, 2, 1, GO!
えっ、なになに？ スクワット？
Eh, what what? Squats?
それスクワットじゃねえし！ 速い速い速い！
That's not a squat! Fast, fast, fast!
Cheating! She's cheating! I didn't!
Oh, I ripped the mind telepathy paper!
Hey, you can't rip our telepathy paper!
13 x 6 = 78!
She's kind of really good at math!
バナナ。またバナナなんだけど！
Banana. It's banana again?!
え？ 2回連続バナナなんだけど！
Eh? It's banana twice in a row?!
Two banana questions! おい、日本語書いてるんじゃねーか！
Two banana questions! Hey, isn't it written in Japanese?!
What?! I was given a handicap because the questions are in English...
...they're written in Japanese! Okay, okay, we got to keep it rolling guys, keep it rolling!
Do I still have to go around and around? Yes! Yes!
Those are the rules by our producers, who are not us!
On my telepathy paper, the next one is... SEXY WALK!
Sexy walk! Do we have to start again if it's not sexy enough?
No! Yes! Huh? Please make up your mind! We'll see!
And... THREE PUSH-UPS! 腕立て3回？
And... THREE PUSH-UPS! 3 push-ups?
Okay, and sexy walk!
Okay, okay, okay! Sexy walk! Sexy jump!
で、セクシーが足りなかったら万が一やり直しって言われてるから。
And if the sexiness is lacking, they said we might have to redo it.
えー！ セクシーが足りない？ Sexy, sexy!
Eh?! Not sexy enough? Sexy, sexy!
任せろ、任せろ！ トワ様...
Leave it to me, leave it to me! Towa-sama...
Okay! Everyone ready?
Okay! Ready! 3, 2, 1, Go!
Sexy Bae!
You tried to be sexy!
1, 2, 3!
トワ様！ Sexy!
Towa-sama! Sexy!
Oh, sexy, sexy! It's not fair! Towa-sama has to take...
Sexy トワちゃん！
Sexy Towa-chan!
あれ？ Sexy Baeは？
Huh? What about Sexy Bae?
Once again!
あれ？ あれ？ Sexyじゃない！
Huh? Huh? That's not sexy!
You tried, but Towa-sama's sexy is like...
You only have to do it on the way there, on the way back you can go straight.
No, no. Hey, hey, don't help the contestant!
Wait!
Name a flower!
Pansy!
Oh, yeah! Pansy!
言ってる？
Did she say it?
Okay! Okay!
1, 1, 1!
Have you been counting the points? Yeah, 1, 1, 1!
Oh, really? 1, 1, 1!
Tiebreaker! Tiebreaker!
Okay, okay, last round! Tiebreaker!
最後のポイントは... 100ポイント！ 100ポイント！
The last point is... 100 points! 100 points!
Can I get rid of this? No! Last round!
Do this, you have to do this well. Okay. Lunge walk!
えー！
Eh?!
きつ！ やばい！
Hard! Crazy!
そして... きた、きた、きた！
And then... Here it comes, here it comes, here it comes!
3回！ Okay, okay! How many times?
3 times! Okay, okay! How many times?
3回！ 3, 3, 3! 3回！
3 times! 3, 3, 3! 3 times!
えー！
Eh?!
Wow, you're so good at that!
頑張ろう！ 頑張ろう！
Let me try! Let me try!
分かりました？
Did you understand?
Okay! Okayです！ 分かりました。
Okay! It's okay! I understood.
しんどそう、なんか。
They look exhausted, somehow.
Can I do this?
No, no, no! Oh, but it will get cut...
Come on, come on. They're fighting!
頑張る！ Ready, everyone? 3, 2, 1, go!
Do your best! Ready, everyone? 3, 2, 1, go!
Go! Go!
Hey, get to the right! 横移動すんの！
Hey, get to the right! Move sideways!
Hey, knees are touching the ground! Towa-sama is fine, she's doing her best.
1, 2! 1, 2, 3!
Oh, she's disqualified!
よいしょ！ よいしょ！ よいしょ！
Yoisho! Yoisho! Yoisho!
トワ様！
Towa-sama!
Wait, let's wait for Bae to come back. Oh, Bae, come on!
Come on Bae, we can answer... Come on Bae.
Come on Bae, we can't decide the winner until you get over here.
はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Hey, you need to high five!
Hey, squat over here. Come on, come on.
Wow!
All right, here's your question.
Say a French word!
Oh! え、ちょっと待って！
Oh! Eh, wait a second!
French... French... 知ってますかね？
French... French... Do they know?
Bonjour!
Oh! Okay!
The winner! The winner!
A winner! A winner! The winner of today!
勝てるわけねぇじゃねぇかよ！
There's no way we could win!
Well, the contestants have something to complain about no matter what we do.
Yeah, we did our best.
The last round was like, insane! やっ てみない？ やってみ... 一周... 一周回って結構広いよ！
The last round was like, insane! Why don't you try? Going around once is actually pretty wide!
No, no, no, no, stop, stop, stop. Bae, Bae only!
Bae only? Bae onlyか！
Bae only? Bae only, huh!
じゃないと... Security! Security!
Otherwise... Security! Security!
Yeah, Security! Don't worry, I got her. Security! Give our winner her crown!
Your crown!
Oh, thank you!
This is unfair! Tiebreak! Tiebreak!
This is Bae. This is Sub. This is Towa.
And you are watching the AutoFist Network!
That rat sucked. Yeah.
Should go back to the gym or something.
She should go back to school and retake PE.
Yeah, but Towa-sama was really strong. Wow, she even got the cool crown! Amazing.
And Sub was so cute! So cute!
Yeah! Yeah!
Also, the hosts were amazing!
The hosts were so beautiful! Every time they were on screen, I was...
...electrified!
I think this is what's gonna get us the funding.
Yeah, I think we're gonna get $10 million for this one.
And the more budget they have, the more difficult the challenges can get, and then...
...the death, you know...
Penalty!
...can be even greater!
Anyways, what if...
...anime...
...but live action?
I don't feel so good.
I'm so tired, Gigi...
Me too! I'm so tired, because I've been working so hard!
I've been working so hard making so many shows! I'm so sleepy after every recording, and I'm doing everything every single day!
I've never had a tea party! Everyone always wanted to invite me to their tea party!
You know what? Actually, I have been preparing something!
Is it this background? / Yes, yes! This realistic background that you probably stole from the internet?
I stole it! I stole it. / Stole it right from the internet? / And this is my tea party, so welcome in!
It's... But yeah, I have one more surprise, Gigi Murin!
A surprise for a tea party? / Yeah. / Where are our models? Where are we? Where is me?
You know what? We got some graphics update!
A graphics update?
You wanna see? You wanna see me? / Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
It's me! Cecilia Immergreen from Hololive English!
Justice! / Wind...
You look great! / Oh, thanks!
You look freaking amazing! / I guess I'll go sit down real quick.
Oh my god, I look so good! Look at my shoes, I look so good!
Hey Gigi, come on, come on in, it's okay! / Oh, I get one too? / Yeah, yeah, yeah!
G'day mate, everyone! It's Gigi Murin from Hololive English Justice!
I'm so happy to be here!
Wow, you look great! / I look great! I guess it's time for me to sit down also.
Look at my shoes too! / Wow, wow!
Wow, those look good! Those look kind of hard to walk in, actually! That's crazy!
No, I'm a natural! Let me sit down. / Sit down, sit down, sit down already!
And together, we are AutoFist!
Finally, we get some time to relax! Wow, you look really good!
Ah, thank... You look really good! / Oh, we're hugging again!
I just really like hugging you! I can't help that I keep hugging you! / I really like hugging, I guess!
Oh, my hood came off! It's fine! / I'm so excited! I'm so excited!
I'm really happy to be here. / Oh, are you hungry? / I'm really hungry! Will you feed me?
Okay, I'll feed you! I'll feed you!
Say ah! / Ah...
Oh, I accidentally dropped it!
Oh, I'm really hungry too, I guess...
Oh my god! You're getting this all over me!
Oh, why are you getting it on your face too? Ew!
Mmm, it tastes sweet! Let me feed you again!
Do you mind if I got my spit on it?
Wait, wait! Let me wipe that off! You got something on the side of your mouth, let me just get that for you!
Let me get it off of you too!
Oh, you have something on your mouth! Okay, okay, that's enough, that's enough!
Are you thirsty? / I'm thirsty! I'm really thirsty!
Okay, I'll pour you some tea!
I'm really excited! / Here's your tea!
It's really hot! / Oh, be careful, be careful!
Oh my god, it's really... Oh my god, it's really hot! Oh, it spilled on my shirt!
It's all over my body! / Oh no, you spilled it! Oh my god, it burns!
Atsui, atsui! Oh my god!
Oh no! I feel like I got a third-degree burn just now!
Why would you do that to me? You're freaking mean! / Sorry! Let me wipe it off of you!
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to do that! I just got really overzealous. Mmm, it's really good now it cooled down! / You like it? What type of tea is it?
It's like a note, a little floral note on it. Here, try some! Try from my finger! Try from my finger!
How's the taste? / Yummy!
That's really good.
Okay, that's enough. I finished my cup. It was really delicious.
If Liz was here, she would tell us that after having a really good meal, we should work out!
Oh yeah! / Yeah, so let me get up.
Let's go stand over there in the corner!
Yeah, let me stand by the horse! That horse is really amazing!
Making so much noise...
Sorry, my shoes are just really big and clunky.
You know what? I think it'd be really cool if we were to do 50 push-ups right now.
I... I want to do...
You know what? I want to do 50 push-ups, too!
Me, I really want to...
No, no, no, I really want to do 50...
Okay, okay, wait, I changed my mind.
I want... I want 50 lunges!
50 lunges?
Oh, your knee hurts?
Yeah, I got into an accident about 200 years ago.
Did you get hit by a car?
I got hit by a car 200 years ago.
Oh, okay. I guess that's just how it is.
You know what, Chichi-murin?
Don't touch me!
Stop touching me!
What? Oh my god! You always do that! Ow!
Why do you always fight with me? You're just...
Ow! You're fighting for no reason! I hate you! Die!
No, I hate you so much! Look at your hair!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Sorry, sorry, sorry! I got mean, I was acting out.
Will you forgive me?
I guess so.
I'm sorry for yelling...
I'm sorry for yelling at you!
And being mean to... Can you kiss my knee, please?
I guess... I feel really good now.
Do you feel better?
I feel better, and I feel really sleepy all of a sudden.
Me too, actually. Yeah, so sleepy...
I'm so sleepy, too!
Ah, but there's only one bed!
What should we do? Should we get in together?
I guess so. I guess we'll get in...
Let me just take off my shoes.
Oh yeah, I think it'd be really, really weird to get into bed with shoes on.
Yeah, that would be strange. Let me help you.
Let me fluff this pillow for you. Oh, you look so...
Here you go, princess.
Let me... Let me just lie down.
Oh, let me get into bed... I'll take my shoes off, too.
I'm already getting so comfortable!
Please, please, I'm going to bed without you!
I'm so tired. If someone doesn't get into bed quick, I'm just going to fall asleep without you.
Oh no, don't, don't!
It's just my achy-achy bones! I'm trying to get into bed, please!
I guess your knee really hurts, still.
It does... Ah, I feel so comfortable!
Thanks for coming to my tea party, Chichi-murin.
Thanks for inviting me, Cici.
Good night. Oh, we're holding hands.
It's because I get scared in the dark.
Oh, of course, yeah.
So I'm glad that we have each other.
Good night, Cici.
Good night, Chichi.
Good night.
I'm Cici!
And I'm Chichi!
And you're watching...
The Autofister Network!
I don't know that's gonna make us any money.
I don't know if that's gonna make us any money.
Well... onto the next idea.
みんなが大好きっ!!
I love everyone!!
延々続行 ルララ Miracle Sing Time
Endless continuation, lalala Miracle Sing Time
歌って 歌って 愛伝える最強手段
Sing, sing, the best way to convey love
つたない曲でも 微妙な歌詞でも
Even with a clumsy melody, even with subtle lyrics
届けたい 精一杯のsoulを
I want to deliver my wholehearted soul
どうしよう オートマティックに決められてる
What to do, it's decided automatically
時間割じゃ追っつかないの
I can't keep up with the timetable
夢無限 したいこと怒濤
Dreams are infinite, what I want to do is surging
廊下もダッシュで集まるよ
Gather together by dashing in the hallway
お行儀悪かったらsorry!
If my manners are bad, sorry!
でもなりふりも構わずに
But without worrying about appearances
どっぷりハマっちゃうplay
Deeply hooked in play
キラリッて もしかこれが青春
Sparkly, could this be youth?
ever ever... Forever Shine
ほんとに大好きっ!!
I really love everyone!!
テンション上昇 ルララ Powerful Gig Time
Tension rising, lalala Powerful Gig Time
ハートって ハートって ワクワク探す天才
Heart, heart, a genius searching for excitement
アレっ!?って言われても ミス連発でも
Even if I'm told "Huh!?", even if I make consecutive mistakes
放ちたい 湧いてくるbraveを
I want to release the welling-up courage
仕掛けるトレモロ 応えるフラム
The tremolo I start, the flam that answers
いいじゃん いいじゃん ノリノリでいいんじゃない
Isn't it fine? Isn't it fine? Isn't it fine to just go with the flow?
ハッピーはいつだってね “今”感じるもの
Happiness is always something you feel right now
宿題よりも重要課題
A task far more important than homework:
放課後のお茶おしゃべり 練習
After-school tea, chatting, and practice!
ユーモア ナチュラル めくるめく笑い ウケ過ぎでお腹痛い
Humor, natural, dizzying laughter—laughing so hard my stomach hurts!
呼吸ぴったし excellent! でも苦手なリフまだあったの
Perfect breath timing, excellent! But there's still a riff I'm bad at...
特訓つきあってくれる? もう少し門限までだって帰りたくない
Will you train with me? Just a bit more until curfew, because I don't wanna go home!
Never never... can't say good-bye
めちゃめちゃ大好きっ!! 超絶ゾッコン ルララ Wonderful Show Time
I love it so, so much!! Super infatuated, lu-la-la, Wonderful Show Time!
音楽って 音楽って もう私達マンマ
Music is, music is... basically us!
スタンディングオベーション 少人数でも
Standing ovation, even if we're a small crowd,
奏でたい 瞬間にrealを
We wanna play the reality of this moment!
昨日の後悔って 明日の心配って
Regrets about yesterday? Worries about tomorrow?
ぶっちゃけぶっちゃけ誰得? なんとく?
Honestly, honestly, who benefits from that? What's the point?
ラッキーはいつだってね “今”掴むもの
Good luck is something you grab in the "now"!
欲張り乙女 あたえられん、さらば
Greedy girls, if we're not given any, then farewell!
どんな本も書いてない 授業じゃちょっと収まんない
It's not written in any textbook, it can't fit in a class lesson!
けど一生忘れない
But I'll never forget it for the rest of my life!
この世にないと思ってた奇跡
The miracle I thought didn't exist in this world—
一緒にね歌えば
If we sing together,
信じられるんだ 強くなれるんだ
I can believe in it, I can become stronger!
みんなが大好きっ!! 延々続行 ルララ Miracle Sing Time
I love everyone so much!! Non-stop continuation, lu-la-la, Miracle Sing Time!
歌って 歌って 愛伝える最強手段
Sing, sing, it's the ultimate way to convey love!
つたない曲でも 微妙な歌詞でも
Even with a clumsy song, even with subtle lyrics,
届けたい 精一杯のsoulを 同心円のlifeを
I wanna deliver with all my soul, a life of concentric circles!
今日は昨日みたい? 明日は今日みたい?
Is today like yesterday? Is tomorrow like today?
だいじょうぶだいじょうぶ 楽しかったら大正解
It's okay, it's okay, if it was fun then it's a huge success!
ロッカーはいつだってね “今”やんちゃ盛り
Rockers are always full of energy in the "now"!
進め乙女 抱きしめて、希望を
Charge forward, girls, embrace hope!
大好き 大好き 大好きをありがとう
Love, love, thank you for all the love!
歌うよ 歌うよ 心こめて今日も歌うよ
I'll sing, I'll sing, with all my heart I'll sing today too!
大好き 大好き 大好きをありがとう
Love, love, thank you for all the love!
歌うよ 歌うよ 愛をこめてずっと歌うよ
I'll sing, I'll sing, with all my love I'll sing forever!
Please hold. We will soon be changing the channel.
Please hold. We are about to switch the channel.
Please wait. The channels will be changed soon.
Please stay seated, as the channels are about to switch.
Don't change the channel, because we'll do it for you.
Do not touch the remote, cause we will be doing it.